Mission: Blighter Mission.
	Type:Supply.
	Target: Mercenary Work.
	Rewards:
		 Type: Supply. Count: 2.
	Penalties:
		 Type: Morale. Count: -1.
	Requirements:
		 One Heavy or Officer or Scout.
	Notes:
		Military Objective: MO_CONVINCE. Convince a group to go along with a plan Examples: Convince the locals to give you the relic. Get bandits to stop attacking trade routes. Get the soldier to give you data..
		Supply Problem: Integration - Logistics support must coordinate well with the existing command structure and strategic planning. Problems - The PCs are working with a corrupt native officer who wonÆt release supplies without a favor. The PCs are being ordered to carry out a delivery according to operational plans that no longer apply and only enemy forces are in the area..
		Supply Type: medical_supplies.

Mission: Breaker Mission.
	Type:Recon.
	Target: Area Recon.
	Rewards:
		 Type: Intel. Count: 2.
	Penalties:
		 Type: Death(s). Count: 2.
	Requirements:
		 One Scout or Sniper.
	Notes:
		It may be that your information can be gained by stealing something or someone.
		Military Objective: MO_COUNTERRECON. Idenify or elminate observers. Examples: Legion suspects a spy is watching the army- find them and eliminate.   Identify Hexed in a village terrorizing the locals. Refugees taken in by Legion have some Hexed that are divulging plans - eliminate them. Convince the enemy that you are a large force at a location by making an attack..

Mission: Vengeful Daze.
	Type:Religious.
	Target: Escort.
	Rewards:
		 Type: Fine Asset. Count: 1.
	Penalties:
		 Type: Morale. Count: -1.
	Requirements:
		 One Officer or Medic.
	Notes:
		Mission has favor of type Holy.
		Consider setting in the context of the Bone Wastes.
		Military Objective: MO_CLEAR. Eliminate all the enemy in a specific area, such as a room in a dungeon. Examples: Remove bandits from a town. Remove monsters from a field. Clean up fleeing troops. Remove troops laying an ambush..

Mission: Grasping Laughter.
	Type:Assault.
	Target: People.
	Rewards:
		 Type: Morale. Count: 3.
	Penalties:
		 Type: Pressure. Count: 1.
	Requirements:
		 One Heavy or Medic or Sniper.
	Notes:
		Your target may be an objective which you need to engage in conflict to achieve.
		Military Objective: MO_BLOCK. Prevent the enemy from accessing an area or advancing along a specific route. Examples: Gandalf on the bridge. Letting an ally escape. delaying an enemy until a trap is set. Keeping enemy out during a ritual..

Mission: Rebel Blade.
	Type:Recon.
	Target: Exfiltration.
	Rewards:
		 Type: Asset. Count: 1.
		 Type: Intel. Count: 1.
	Penalties:
		 Type: Pressure. Count: 1.
	Requirements:
		 One Scout or Sniper.
	Notes:
		Mission is especially dangerous.  Consider adding a lieutenant or elite.
		It may be that your information can be gained by stealing something or someone.
		Military Objective: MO_DISENGAGE. Reach a specific area, away from the enemy that will allow them to escape with no chance of immediately successful pursuit. Examples: You failed original engagement roll and encontered a huge force - get away. An ally is surrounded- you need to free them and then disengage..
